<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ala-alrababah.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ala Alrababah</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/home/</guid>
      <description>I am an Assistant Professor in the Department of Social and Political Sciences at Bocconi University. I am also a member of the Evidence in Governance and Politics (EGAP) network, a faculty affiliate with the Immigration Policy Lab (IPL) at ETH Zurich and Stanford University, a research fellow at the BAFFI Center on Economics, Finance and Regulation and the Dondena Center for Research on Social Dynamics and Public Policy at Bocconi University, and an invited researcher at the Abdul Latif Jameel Poverty Action Lab (J-PAL).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description> You can download my CV here. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/data/</guid>
      <description>We combined data from UNHCR’s Syrian refugees per locality in Lebanon (as defined by UNHCR, from December 2018) with data on Lebanese voters per locality (using the 2018 elections). The data can be accessed here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other writing</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/writing/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Refugee Return: Key Findings, Gaps, and Future Research. World Bank/UNHCR - Joint Data Centre.
With Marine Casalis
Cited by: UNHCR Global Trends Report 2024
Knowledge about COVID-19 among Syrian Refugees in Lebanon. Innovations for Poverty Action.
With Marine Casalis, Dominik Hangartner, Daniel Masterson, and Jeremy Weinstein
Syria and some host governments want refugees to go home. What do refugees think?. The Monkey Cage, The Washington Post.
With Marine Casalis and Daniel Masterson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Publications Reducing Attrition in Phone-based Panel Surveys: A Web Application to Facilitate Best Practices and Semi-Automate Survey Workflow Political Science Research and Methods. First View.
With Marine Casalis, Daniel Masterson, Dominik Hangartner, Stefan Wehrli, and Jeremy Weinstein.
The Free Movement of People and the Success of Far-Right Parties: Evidence from Switzerland’s Border Liberalization American Political Science Review. First View. With Andreas Beerli, Dominik Hangartner, and Dalston Ward.
Media: Foreign Policy, NRC</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>I have worked as teaching assistant for courses in quantitative methods, comparative politics, international relations, and Middle East politics. These courses include:
Methods II: Introduction to Quantitative Methods (Dominik Hangartner, Masters Students at ETH Zurich, Fall 2021)
War and Peace in American Foreign Policy (Kenneth Schultz, Stanford University, Spring 2018)
Middle Eastern Politics (Lisa Blaydes, Stanford University, Fall 2017)
Islam, Iran, and the West (Abbas Milani, Stanford University, Spring 2017)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
