<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ala-alrababah.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> </title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/home/</guid>
      <description>window.dataLayer = window.dataLayer || []; function gtag(){dataLayer.push(arguments);} gtag(&#39;js&#39;, new Date()); gtag(&#39;config&#39;, &#39;UA-154134423-1&#39;);   
  
Welcome! I am a PhD candidate in political science at Stanford University, a graduate fellow at the Immigration Policy Lab (IPL), and a PhD fellow at the Center on Philanthropy and Civil Society. My primary research is in comparative politics and international relations with a focus on authoritarian media, political violence, and migration and refugees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>  You can download my CV here.  If this browser does not support PDFs. Please download the PDF to view it: Download PDF.
 -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/data/</guid>
      <description>We combined data from UNHCR’s Syrian refugees per locality in Lebanon (as defined by UNHCR, from December 2018) with data on Lebanese voters per locality (using the 2018 elections). The data can be accessed here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other writing</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/writing/</guid>
      <description>Quantitative Text Analysis of Arabic News Media. MENA Politics Newsletter, Volume 2, Issue 2 Fall 2019
 Jordan shut out 60,000 Syrian refugees and then saw a backlash. This is why (with Scott Williamson). Monkey Cage Blog, The Washington Post. 2018.
   Jordan’s Danger Zone: The Perils of Building a Safe Haven in Syria. Foreign Affairs. 2015.
 Taking on Operation Dawn: The Creeping Advance of the Islamic State in Western Libya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Publications Authoritarian Media and Diversionary Threats: Lessons from Thirty Years of Syrian State Discourse. Political Science Research and Methods.
With Lisa Blaydes.
Scholars have long argued that leaders manipulate foreign policy, sometimes even initiating wars in order to enhance their domestic political position. But diversionary wars are relatively rare given the high costs of conflict. In this project, we examine data from major Syrian daily newspapers over a thirty-year period (1987-2018) to explore how autocratic regimes use diversionary rhetoric.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description> 
I have worked as teaching assistant for courses in comparative politics, international relations, and Middle East politics. These courses include:
 War and Peace in American Foreign Policy (Kenneth Schultz, Spring 2018)
 Middle Eastern Politics (Lisa Blaydes, Fall 2017)
 Islam, Iran, and the West (Abbas Milani, Spring 2017)
 U.S. Relations with Iran (Abbas Milani, Fall 2016)
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>