<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ala-alrababah.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> </title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/home/</guid>
      <description>window.dataLayer = window.dataLayer || []; function gtag(){dataLayer.push(arguments);} gtag(&#39;js&#39;, new Date()); gtag(&#39;config&#39;, &#39;UA-154134423-1&#39;);   
  
/* Define a margin before h2 element */ h2 { margin-top: 6em; } /* Define a margin after every first p elements */ p:first-of-type { margin-bottom: 3em; }  #r-markdown { margin-top: 0em; } #r-markdown p:first-of-type { margin-bottom: 3em; }  Welcome! I am a Postdoctoral Fellow at the Immigration Policy Lab (IPL) at ETH Zurich.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>  You can download my CV here.  If this browser does not support PDFs. Please download the PDF to view it: Download PDF.
 -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/data/</guid>
      <description>We combined data from UNHCR’s Syrian refugees per locality in Lebanon (as defined by UNHCR, from December 2018) with data on Lebanese voters per locality (using the 2018 elections). The data can be accessed here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other writing</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/writing/</guid>
      <description>Syria and some host governments want refugees to go home. What do refugees think? (with Marine Casalis and Daniel Masterson). The Monkey Cage, The Washington Post. December 2020.
 The Ministry of Made-Up Pages: Yemen-Based Actors Impersonate Government Agencies to Spread Anti-Houthi Content (with Shelby Grossman, Josh A. Goldstein, Natasha Patel, Shelby Perkins, and Abuzar Royesh)
 Returning Home? Conditions in Syria, Not Lebanon, Drive the Return Intentions of Syrian Refugees (with Daniel Masterson, Marine Casalis, Dominik Hangartner, Jeremy Weinstein, and Nasser Yassin) Innovations for Poverty Action Policy Brief September 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Publications Can Exposure to Celebrities Reduce Prejudice? Estimating the Effect of Mohamed Salah on Islamophobic Attitudes and Behaviors American Political Science Review
With William Marble, Salma Mousa, and Alexandra Siegel.
 Selected media coverage: BBC Arabic, The Economist, The Times, Fox News, The Daily Mail, Sky News, Vice, The Independent, The National, Spiegel Online, Le Figaro, la Republica, Al Jazeera, EuroNews, Al-Masry Al-Youm, Al-Araby Al-Jadeed.
 DM&amp;amp;E Webinar presentation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ala-alrababah.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description> 
I have worked as teaching assistant for courses in comparative politics, international relations, and Middle East politics. These courses include:
 War and Peace in American Foreign Policy (Kenneth Schultz, Spring 2018)
 Middle Eastern Politics (Lisa Blaydes, Fall 2017)
 Islam, Iran, and the West (Abbas Milani, Spring 2017)
 U.S. Relations with Iran (Abbas Milani, Fall 2016)
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
